-太棒了  -兄弟  别一看大比赛
- All right! Yes! - Hey, man, don't touch my shin
就狂拍我的腿
every time there's a big play.
好的  行了  我知道了
Yeah, no, I got it.
-太棒了  -别每次都碰我
- Oh, yes! - Don't touch it every time!
兄弟  停停
Hey, man, stop.
太棒了
Oh! There it is!
-停下  -尼克
- No! - Hey, Nick.
杰茜把内裤忘在烘干机里了
Um, Jess left her panties in the dryer.
我把它们拿出来你不介意吧
You mind if I move 'em?
当然不介意
Sure, man, I don't care.
等等  你问我干什么
Wait a second. Why do you ask?
你不是要借机做什么猥琐的事吧
You're not gonna move them in a weird way or something, are you?
不  兄弟  我只是表示下尊重而已
No, dude, I'm just trying to be respectful, that's all.
你跟杰茜在一起之前
You know, before you and Jess were together,
我帮她收过上百次内裤  所以
I moved her panties hundreds of times, so...
-等等  什么  -上百次
- Wait, what? - Hundreds of times?
什么  难道你就跟内裤偷窥狂一样
What, are you just hanging around the-the dryer
没事就在烘干机附近转悠吗
like some sort of panty-hawk?
-什么  -内裤偷窥狂
- What? - Panty-hawk.
我看过那部剧
I'd watch that show.
那我是把它们拿出来呢  还是
So should I just go move them, or...
尼克  他开始猥琐了  你去收吧
Nick, he's being weird. You gotta move 'em.
所以我现在是收内裤的了
Oh, so now I'm the panty mover?
你是她男朋友
Yeah, you're the boyfriend.
还有这种道理
That's not a life!
到底谁去收那些内裤
Who the hell is gonna move the panties?
教练  你去收
Coach, you move 'em.
把它们拿出来 感受一下余温
Are they warm from the dryer?
知道吗  你出局了
You know what? You're out.
-成熟点  我去收内裤  -谢谢
- Grow up. I'll move the panties. - Thank you.
你好像特别热心啊
Oh, seems awfully eager.
是啊  你也太热心了  施密特
Yeah, you're awfully eager, here, Schmidt.
对  我这一生
Oh, yeah. I been,
都在等着收你女朋友的内裤
I've been waiting my entire life to move your girlfriend's panties...
别再说"内裤"了  兄弟
Stop saying "panties", bro.
内裤
Panties.
不  是内裤
No, they're panties.
重音在"裤"  内裤
With a "d". Pandies.
小内裤
Pandies.
像正常人一样说"内裤"这个词
Say "panties" like a normal person.
不  黑人是这么说的
No, this is how black people say it.
把你的"内裤"脱下来
Pull your "pannies" down.
我们就是这么说"内裤"的
We say "pannies". Yeah.
白人是这么说的
Here's how a white dude says it.
把你的内裤脱下来
Pull your panties down.
兄弟们  说实话  你们没发现
Guys, honestly, can you not see
内裤影响了我们的感情吗
what the panties are doing to us?
说到杰茜就别提"内裤"这个词
Stop saying "panties" when it comes to Jess...everybody.
这就是我们不该跟女人住一起的原因
This is exactly why none of us should live with a woman.
我想到了个办法
I've got an idea.
你们绝对不会相信
You guys are never gonna believe what...
随便你们疯
You know what? I don't care.
刚刚发生了一件不可思议的事
The most amazing thing just happened.
开车长点眼睛
Watch where you're going! Hey!
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
-天哪  -对不起
- Oh, boy. - Sorry.
对不起  是我的错
Sorry, my bad.
我们以为自己死定了
We thought we were gonna die,
但她是真的很内疚
but she was actually really sorry.
所以她邀请我们  去她老板家参加派对
So she invited us to a party at her boss's house,
他们还会派豪华轿车来接我们
and they're sending a limo,
猜猜她的老板是谁
and guess who her boss is.
是王子  是王子啊
It's Prince! It's Prince!
普林斯·罗杰斯·内尔森  美国著名歌手  以胆大敢为，性格颇为古怪而著称
是王子  是王子  王子  是王子
It's Prince. It's Prince. Prince! It's Prince!
翻译：瑶莞莞 麦田守望者 MythCreator
-什么  真棒  -是王子吗
- What? Whoa! Nice! - Oh! Prince?
我们要去参加  在王子家举办的派对
We're going to a party at Prince's house,
翻译：持久君 小明漫画家 扭扭布
-我们要去参加派对  -我们要去
- we're going to a party... - we're going...
-在王子家  -我们要去了
- ...at Prince's house. - We're going!
时间轴：糖不甩   后期：MythCreator
校对：麦田守望者 丢丢曳  总监:  丢丢曳
那不是我的内裤
That's not my underwear.
杰茜驾到  第三季  第十四集
我该穿哪双鞋去王子家
Which shoes should I wear to Prince's house?
白的还是黑的
White or black?
白的还是黑的  尼克  快帮我看看
White, or black? Nick, come on.
豪华轿车随时会到
The limo's gonna be here any minute.
穿哪双鞋呢  白的还是黑的
Which shoe? White or black?
我觉得你穿什么都好看
Well, I think you look great in everything.
我只想这一刻快点过去
I just want this moment to end.
你那些露趾鞋呢
What are your open-toe options?
没一双合适的
None of it works, okay?
我们得重新开始  来吧
We gotta start over. Let's go.
你输了  兄弟
You failed, bro.
兄弟  我很高兴不用去那个派对
Man, I am glad I'm not going to that party.
压力太大了  不是吗
Too much pressure, am I right?
老兄   如果是在高中
Dude, in high school,
能参加王子的派对  你就算梦想成真了
going to a Prince party would've been your dream come true.
你那时候对他可着迷了
You were obsessed.
*今晚我们要去参加派对*
*So tonight we're gonna party*
*就像1999年那样*
*Like it's 1999*
你真恶心  米勒
You suck, Miller!
我妈最后把裤子剪开才能帮我脱了下来
My mother had to cut those pants off me,
包得实在太紧了
they were so tight.
亲爱的各位
Dearly beloved...
今日我们欢聚在此
we are gathered here today
来欢庆这件叫做
to celebrate this thing called...
施密特的事
Schmidt.
-尼克  你穿的是工装裤吗  -是啊
- Nick, are you wearing cargo pants? - Yeah.
你就穿这个去参加高大上的派对
You're gonna wear those to an A-list party?
伙计们  我们应该怎样运输这些货物呢
Hey, guys, how are we going to transport all this cargo?
哦对了  我们有尼克的裤子  不用愁了
Oh, wait, we have nick's pants. We're saved.
快把这裤子脱掉
Get the frickin' pants off.
哥们  又不是我们去
Dude, we're not going.
王子邀请的是辣妹们  不是四个大老爷们
Prince invited the hot girls, not the four dudes.
什么
What?
那我买两千刀的西装是闹哪样
Why did I buy this $2,000 suit?
你个二货
You idiot!
哥们  我的西装只要两百刀
Dude, my suit cost $200,
而且翻领上还订着袜子
and mine came with socks stapled to the lapel.
-不会击掌的  -我也不会  -因为...
- Not gonna tap that. - I'm not gonna, - 'cause... yeah.
因为是附送的
'cause it came with it.
附送袜子
Yeah, but it came with socks.
不可接受
Unacceptable!
这个派对本该把我带去下一个等级的
This party was supposed to take me to the next level.
-什么等级  -最好别问
- Next level of what? - Don't ask, man.
在每个男人的一生中
In every man's life,
会有一个可以改变一切的派对
there is one party that changes everything.
你们不会懂的
You don't understand.
这就是为什么我远远超越了你们
And that is exactly why I'm leaving you all behind.
所以这么久以来  你只是在等待结交更酷的小伙伴
So this whole time, you've just been waiting for cooler friends?
是的  当然
Yes. Of course.
教练  看看周围
Coach, look around.
这绝不能是终点线
This can't be the finish line.
主角来了
Here she is.
哇
Whoa!
你看起来美极了
You look great!
施密特为什么也盛装打扮了
Why is Schmidt dressed up?
哥不想回答
I don't want to talk about it.
王子
Prince!
难以置信
Unbelievable!
看呀
Hey, look!
我在豪华轿车里
I'm in a limo!
我真希望我有一对大长腿
I wish I had really long legs
这样就能占满大轿车里的空间了
so I could stretch 'em out the length of the limo.
玩的开心
Well, have fun.
我爱你
I love you.
刚刚尼克是不是第一次
Did Nick just tell me
-说他爱我  -是的
- he loved me for the first time? - Yeah.
然后我用指枪来回应他了
And did I do finger guns back?
是的  你是这么做了
Yeah, you did.
-完了...  -是啊
- No... - Yes.
你会想把这个全喝掉的
You're gonna want to drink all of this.
司机大哥
Hey, driver,
我们需要更多的香槟
we're gonna need some more champagne!
那...
So...
好吧...
Yeah...
哥们  男人从来不会先说那句话的  好吗
Dude, a man never says it first, okay?
我也没计划要对她说
Well, it wasn't my plan to tell her,
就是脱口而出了  她看起来美极了
it just slipped out. She looked so pretty.
尼克  你真是那么想的吗  你爱她吗
Well, Nick, is that how you feel? I mean, do you love her?
当然了
Of course I do.
但我没准备像那样说出来
But I wasn't gonna say it like that.
我本打算时机成熟时再说的  温斯顿
I was gonna wait, Winston.
你只是脱口而出了  没什么大不了的
You blurted it out. It's not a big deal.
我经常这么干
That's what I always do.
我爱你
I love you!
有时她们也说爱我  有时不会...
Sometimes they say it back, sometimes they don't...
它就是个概率游戏
I mean, it's like a numbers game.
我总是这样
I always do this.
我总是变得过于紧张  把妹纸们吓到了
I always get too intent, and then I freak girls out.
我搞砸了  我该干嘛
I blew it. What do I do?
尼克  覆水难收了
Well, Nick, you can't take it back.
那也不一定
Well, that's not 100% true.
哎哟我去  王子的豪宅
Damn! Prince's house!
不赖嘛  王子
Not bad, Prince!
你们觉得王子有泳池吗
You think Prince has a pool?
你们觉得他有吊桥吗
You think he has a drawbridge?
我们进不去
We're never gonna get in.
我们甚至开的都不是豪车
We're not even in a limo.
不好意思  我们坐的是福特蒙迪欧
Uh, excuse me, we're in a Ford Fusion,
有史以来最好的车
the best car ever made.
同样的油耗它能跑两倍的路程
It gets double the gas mileage of...
闭嘴
Shut up.
你这一路就光说这个了
That's all you've been talking about the whole drive,
有点怪怪的
and it's weird.
你一说这个的时候就性致勃勃的
You get sexual when you talk about it.
你眼睛都快喷出火了  我不喜欢这样
It's in your eyes. I don't like it.
同样的油耗跑两倍的距离
Double the gas mileage means you go double as far.
-意味着很长  -闭嘴
- That means long. - Shut up!
我可以把车借给你  哥们  你自己感受下
I'll let you borrow this, dude, and you'll feel it.
-你会明白我说的...  -干嘛不现在就让我试试
- You'll know what I'm talking... - Why don't I feel it right now?
-来感受一下  -呦呼
- Feel it. - Oh, cowabunga!
冲浪术语  用于冲浪手战胜巨浪后在冲浪板上庆祝
-你感受到了吗  -我想打你脸
- You felt it? - I'm gonna punch you in the face.
开你的车吧
Just drive the car.
你以前从来没被油耗激怒过吗
You've never been turned on by gas mileage before?
-从来没有  -没有  -有过一次
- Never. - No! - Once.
什么时候
When was that?
是周四  我只记得这个
It was a Thursday, that's all I remember.
-周四  -是的
- A Thursday? - Yeah.
开车吧
Just drive the car.
我得去告诉我的女友我不爱她
I gotta go tell my girlfriend I don't love her
-所以她才不会甩了我  -好吧
- so she doesn't leave me. - All right.
像个正常人
Like a normal person.
太棒了
Amazing.
你能相信吗
Can you believe it?
不  我不能
No, I can't.
指枪  太白痴了
Finger guns? That was so stupid.
我脑子都呆住了
My brain just froze.
如果那开豪车的家伙没把车开走
If the limo guy hadn't pulled away,
我也许就能做整套的套索手势了
I probably would've done a lasso.
我觉得你只是有点被吓到了
I think you were just a little scared.
被什么吓到
Scared of what?
说了我爱你
Saying "I love you"?
我经常说我爱你
I say "I love you" all the time.
-我现在就说  我爱你  -我也爱你
- I'll say right now. I love you. - I love you!
我是克莱顿·克萧[这真是他本人]
Hi, I'm Clayton Kershaw.
在洛杉矶道奇队效力
I'm a Los Angeles Dodger.
洛杉矶道奇：美国职业棒球大联盟的一支球队
克莱顿·克萧为该队先发投手
我是杰茜卡·戴
Yeah, and I'm Jessica Day.
我是洛杉矶航天员
I'm a Los Angeles astronaut.
现在不是时候  伙计
Not now, pal.
-他不可能让我们进去  -那怎么办
- He's never gonna let us in. - So what do we do?
镇静点  我和你一样想进去
Pull it together. I need this as much as you do.
我的新生命在那个宴会里等着我呢
My new life is waiting for me in that party.
伙计们  听着  我在想也许现在是
Guys, look, I can't help but think that now might be a good time
玩冰火岛的好时候
For a little fire and ice.
冰火岛：一款经典木制桌游
曾于2003年赢得门萨高智商精选选择冠军
-别  -绝对不  -不要
- Please... - There is never... - Oh! no!
-玩冰火岛的好时候  -来吧
- A good time for fire and ice. - Yes! yeah!
冰火岛能让你加入大学的聚会
Fire and ice got you into parties in college,
但无法让你进入王子的家
but it's not getting you into Prince's house.
温斯顿  冰与火混合起来会发生什么
Winston, what happens when you mix fire and ice?
得到温水  宝贝
Warm water, baby.
丢死个人了
This is embarrassing.
-是气泡  -冒泡啦
- It's bubbling. - It's bubbling, baby!
温水  温水
Warm water! warm water!
-温水  -温水
- Warm water! -Warm water!
我在名单上
Um, yeah, I'm on the list.
厄尼
Ernie!
温尼
Winnie?!
温斯顿·L·毕夏普
Winston L. Bishop.
厄尼  真是你吗  我的上帝啊
Ernie, is that really you? Oh, my goodness!
快过来
Come here, man!
这个人救过我的命
This guy saved my life, man.
不  是你救过我的命
No, you saved my life.
我问你个问题
Let me ask you something, man.
你和弗雷迪还有联系吗
You still keep in contact with Freddy?
弗雷迪没能撑下来
Freddy didn't make it.
弗雷迪死了
Freddy's gone?
不  别这样  没有
No! come on! No! No, man!
我们不是在哭
We ain't crying.
不对  你哭了  我也哭了
No, you cry, I cry.
这是个美妙的夜晚
This is a great night.
希望不要出岔子
Hope nothing ruins it.
看着好温馨
That's nice to see.
进去吧  你们
Come on, you guys.
-致弗雷迪  -致弗雷迪
- For Fsreddy. - For Freddy.
-很了不起  -这都行
- That's remarkable. - That worked?
我们需要我们自己的冰火岛  伙计
We need our own fire and ice, pal.
好吧
Well, all right, man.
火腿加芝士
Ham and cheese!
我真的不觉得名字能起什么效果
I don't really think the name made a...
火腿加芝士
Ham and cheese!
尼克  我们应该排练一下
Nick, we should reherse!
借过  借过
Excuse me. Excuse me!
-怎么  这家伙是谁  -尼克·米勒
- What?! Who's this guy? - Nick Miller?
-那是施密特吗  -你个混蛋
- Is that Schmidt? - You scoundrel, you.
老天  过来  很高兴见到你
Well, hot damn. Come here. It's good to see you.
我可没那么高兴见到你
Yeah, well, the feeling's not mutual!
上一次我见到他  是在沙漠里
The last time I saw him, I was on the desert,
他正要把我母亲送进监狱
and he was putting my mother into a prison.
你不明白我们在做什么  是不是
You don't understand what we're doing, do you?
让这个畜生离我远点
Keep this animal away from me!
你知道吗  那是我的错
You know what? It's my fault.
我们没排练过  我们没排练过
We didn't rehearse. We didn't rehearse.
我们能参加聚会了吗
Can we come into the party?
你知道吗  我们得在这里等着
You know what? We're gonna wait back here.
我知道  是我的错  是我
I get it. It's my fault, it's...
尼克
Nick...?
我是藏在一群模特里的特洛伊木马
I'm Trojan horsing inside a bunch of models.
一切为自己
Every ham for himself.
不  尼克  让我进去
No, Nick! Let me in there!
模特们  让我进去  拜托
Models, let me in, please.
-不  先生  -放开我
- No, sir. - Unhand me!
杰茜  你在这里  抱歉
Jess? Hey, there you are. Excuse me.
杰茜  尼克
Jess. Nick, hi!
你在这里做什么呢
What are you doing here?!
-真高兴见到你  -是啊
- I'm so happy to see you! - Yeah.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in?
-我有话要跟你说  -我知道
- I need to talk to you. - I know.
我没法就让事情这样
I can't leave it the way that was.
我知道  因为...有些事
I know, because... there's something, um,
我当时真应该说的
I really should have said back there
而我没有
and I didn't, and, um...
我觉得很有必要对你说
I think it's important that I say to you.
所以  我想说的是  尼克·米勒
So, uh, what I wanted to say is, Nick Miller...
我...
I...
杰茜
Jess!
她没事
She's all right.
杰茜  你没事吧
Hey, Jess, you okay?
嗨
Hi.
发生什么了
What happened?
你恐慌发作晕倒了
You had a panic attack and you fell down.
天哪
Oh, my God...
其实比指枪还要糟糕
Which is actually worse than finger guns.
我以为那不可能会发生的
I didn't think that was possible.
恰当地说
I think it's fair to say
应该是我没能很好地控制局面
that I did not handle the situation very well.
不  听着  这没什么
No, look, it's fine.
事实上  我想收回之前说的一切  杰茜
In fact, I want to take the whole thing back, Jess.
什么
What?
我不该那么说的  那是个意外  而且
I shouldn't have said it, it was an accident and, uh...
算是澄清事实吧
Yeah, so just kind of clear the air.
不  不  尼克
No! No, Nick!
这下可相当尴尬了
This just got very awkward.
坚强点  尼克
Be strong, Nick!
什么
What did...?
-什么  -那是什么  -谁在讲话
- What...? - What's that? - Who said that?
我在树篱外面
I'm outside the hedge!
看见我手臂了吗
You see my arm?
我正努力爬过来
I'm trying to push through!
你在那上面干什么
What are you doing up there?
小心点
Be careful!
我忍不了了
I lost my bearings!
不得不爬到高处躲开那些蜘蛛
I had to go high to avoid the spiders!
尼克
Nick...
先等他搞完吧
Just wait for him to finish.
我要过来了
I'm breaching!
小心点  小心点
Easy! Easy!
王子的飞盘技术真烂
Prince is terrible at frisbee.
那边大概有十多个这东西
There's, like, ten of these things up there.
伙计们  我能和尼克单独谈会儿吗
Hey, guys, can I talk to Nick alone for a second?
没问题
You got it.
当然
Sure.
你要收回你的话吗
You're taking it back?
你真是那么觉得的吗
Is that how you really feel?
这个嘛...
Well...
你是什么感觉
How do you feel?
嗨
Hi.
我是王子
I'm Prince.
所以有什么问题吗
So what seems to be the problem?
我太唐突了
Oh, how rude of me.
受惊吓的时间都没给你们
I haven't given you enough time to freak out yet.
你们现在可以了
You may do so now.
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
我的天哪  尼克
Oh, my God! Nick!
我不是很懂"指枪"这个词
I'm not familiar with this term "Finger Guns."
你们能仔细描述一下吗
Can you elaborate?
好的  像这样...
Uh, yeah, it's a...
别对我做那个  我会会错意的
Whoa. Don't point those at me. They might go off.
相当的王子式幽默
That was very much of your flavor of humor.
听着  尼克
Listen, Nick, uh...
尼克  对吧
Nick, right?
对  我是叫尼克
Yes, that's my name.
杰茜和我要
Jess and I are gonna take a moment
单独待一会儿
to just be alone.
我不担心  但是为什么
I'm-I'm not worried, but why?
你要跟她说些什么
What are you gonna talk to her about?
你
You.
尼克  我从没想过我会这么说  但是
Nick, I never thought I'd say this, but...
我得跟王子单独待会儿
I need to be alone with Prince.
那好吧
All right, well...
好
Yeah.
你喜欢煎饼吗
So, do you like pancakes?
希希  快帮忙  保镖跟着我呢
Cece, help! The bouncer's after me.
-没问题  -好的
- Oh, all right. - Okay.
他走了
He's gone.
他走了  施密特
He's gone, Schmidt.
他走了吗
Is he gone?
你可以停下来了
You can stop now.
他可固执了  他肯定会回来的
He's tenacious. He's definitely gonna be back.
我保证没事了
Pretty sure it's all clear.
看见老朋友总是很开心
It's always good to see old friends.
谢谢你
Thank you.
今晚我们不计前嫌
Tonight's the night we're just gonna leave this all behind
做更好的朋友  对吗
and get cooler friends, right?
对  没错
Yeah, right.
我们本应该死了  我们本应该不在了
We should be dead. We should be dead.
我从没有想过还能再见到他
I never thought I was gonna see him again!
他现在很动感情  因为这都是真的
He's getting emotional right now, because this is real.
如果你哭了  我也会哭的
Oh, if you cry, I'm gonna cry.
然后我也会哭  我们可以一起哭
And then I'm gonna cry, then we can just cry together.
可怜的弗雷迪
Poor Freddy.
杰茜和王子在一起  而我喝了不少了
Jess is with Prince! And I've been drinking.
等等  杰茜和王子在一起
Wait -- Jess is with Prince?
-我喝了不少了  这俩是谁  -拜托  伙计
- And I've been drinking. Who are these two? - Come on, man,
冰火姐妹花  兄弟  别碍事
Fire and Ice, dude. Get out.
-越来越热了是吧  -没错
- It's getting warm in here isn't it? - Yes.
其实有点小冷  我们...
It's actually a little chilly. We're...
饶了我吧  我知道你要干嘛
Oh, give me a break. I see what you're doing.
你想色诱我
You're trying to tempt me sexually.
没兴趣
Not interested.
你在干什么  尼克
What are you doing, Nick?
你脱  导致我也脱
That leads to me taking my jacket off,
然后突然间  你们就成功让我失身了
and all of a sudden, you guys got me in my underwear, huh?
我不是傻子  散个步去吧  大家没兴趣
I'm not a dummy. Take a walk. No one's interested.
-真没礼貌  真可笑  -我们还有事  粗鲁吗
- So rude. How idiotic. - We got business. Rude?
不不不  别走  别走
No, no, no, no, no, no, stay, stay, stay.
-我们走  -傻瓜
- Let's go. - Idiot!
没错  我是傻瓜
Yeah, I'm an idiot.
-再见  -不不  不要再见
- Ciao. - No, no, no ciao!
不要再见
No ciao.
在你们说
You'll be replaced by robots
"弗莱基-卡瓦-利吉斯"之前
before you can say,
你们就会被机器人顶替的
"fragi-cava-licious."
-你拒绝了姐妹花  -没错  伙计
- You're bringing fire and ice down! - Yeah, man.
你怎么能拒绝冰火姐妹花呢
You don't bring fire and ice down.
别冲我来
Don't start with me right now.
我今天够郁闷了  谁还在乎她们
I'm having a terrible day. Who cares about them?
谁在乎  我在乎
Who cares? I care!
我现在突然想跳舞
I feel like dancing right now.
跳舞解决不了问题
Dancing's not the answer.
你不会跳舞
You can't dance.
跳舞只会让你更郁闷
It's only gonna get worse.
来把这里闹翻天吧
Let's tear the roof off this joint,
让王子知道我们的厉害
and show Prince how we do!
谢谢  查尔斯
Thanks, Charles.
你想知道为什么
You want to know why
自己无法对那个不错的家伙说"爱"吗
you can't tell that nice dude you love him?
我想说  但是...
I want to say it, but...
你害怕了
You're scared.
没错
Exactly.
如果你说了  而你们又不能白头偕老怎么办
If you say it and things don't work out, what then?
我真的很在意他
I really care for him.
我只是担心
And I'm just worried
会失去他
I'm gonna lose him.
傻话
That's stupid.
你才傻
You're stupid.
原谅你了
I forgive you.
-天啊  感谢上帝  -而且
- Oh, my God, thank God! - Besides...
为一切美丽的事物受伤
anything beautiful
都是值得的
is worth getting hurt for.
说得真好
Well, that's very well put.
你知道这话出自谁吗
You know who said that?
不知道
No.
我
Me.
你真棒  天啊
You're good. God.
我以前怎么没有这么喜欢你呢  王子
I wish I were more like you, Prince.
把薄饼吃完
Finish your pancake.
然后继续开工
Let's get to work.
真的很好吃
Oh, it's really good.
但是我已经撑得慌了
But I'm super full.
-吃掉  -好吧
- Pancake. - Okay.
来  穿上
Here, put this on.
好漂亮
Oh, that's beautiful,
但我觉得  我穿上太糟蹋了
but I don't think I could pull that off.
别多说了
Don't argue with me.
好吧
Okay.
跟着我说
Repeat after me.
-爱  -爱
- Love. - Love.
十四比零  我领先
14-zero. My lead.
你到底想教我什么
What am I supposed to be learning here?
十五比零
15-zero.
-爱  -爱
- Love. - Love.
你说的还是不对
You're not saying it right.
现在明白了吗
Do you understand now?
是的  我猜我明白了
Yes, I think I do.
现在呢
What about now?
不明白了
No.
不懂
看看里面
Look in there.
等等  停  不要  我怕黑
Wait, stop, no! I'm afraid of the dark!
我说过  别害怕
I said stop being afraid.
这才叫性感
Yeah! This is what sexy is!
你觉得怎么样
So, what do you think?
我觉得你应该去找尼克了
I think you need to go find Nick.
我不知道要怎么感谢你
I don't know how to thank you.
我真心一个字都没听到
I honestly didn't hear a word you said.
好的
Okay.
好  我懂了
Okay, gotcha.
现在这是你的派对了
This is your party now.
-去贵宾房吗   -是的
- To the VIP room? - Yeah.
和你们去吗
With the two of you?
你不可能做得到
You can't handle it!
你无法战胜我
You can't beat me!
加油  就快了
Come on. You've got it.
伙计  你不行的
Boy, you don't got it.
你不行的
You can't do it.
-你能做到的  -三
- You're gonna do it. - Three...
-你做不到的  -二...  -他就要做到了
- You can't do it. - Two... - He's gonna do it!
加油  你能行的
Come on, now, you can get it.
温尼 别放弃
Winnie, don't give up.
-怎么样  -真见鬼
- What? - Damn it.
-非常厉害  -新纪录
- That's impressive. - New record.
周围都是名人和土豪
Surrounded by celebrities and millionaires,
你们这些蠢货竟然在比赛空口吃柠檬
and you dingbats are playing lemon mouth.
放马过来吧  小妞
Rind me, woman.
-来真的吗  -好  来吧
- Really? - Okay, here we go.
-开始吧  -好  开始
- Let's do it. - All right, let's go.
好戏开始了
Let's get this party started.
你光辉过了  温斯顿
You've got the time, Winston.
-见识一下吧  -好了  来吧
- Check this out. - All right, let's go.
十  九
Ten, nine,
-你在干什么  -八...
- What are you doing? - Eight...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
砰
Boom!
-不是吧  -你不该吃掉柠檬的
- What?! - You're not supposed to eat the lemon.
新纪录
New record.
游戏都不是这样的
That's not even the game!
尼克·米勒
Nick Miller!
杰茜
Hey, Jess.
我并不为我说的话感到抱歉
I'm not sorry that I said it.
我不想这么说  但我根本听不见你说什么
I hate to say this, but I couldn't hear you
这太吵了
'cause it's very loud.
我爱你
I love you!
我爱你  尼克·米勒
I love you, Nick Miller!
你穿的是什么
What the hell are you wearing?
王子信任我
Prince trusts me.
太棒了
Awesome!
是啊
Yeah!
今晚有人想坠入爱河吗
Anybody want to fall in love tonight?
天啊
Oh, my God!
天哪
*难道  难道你不想*
*Don't? Don't you wanna*
*今晚坠入爱河吗*
*Fall in love tonight*
*她说*
*She said*
*美妙的夜晚  我最爱的旋律*
*Special night, my favorite tune*
*月色撩人  她跳丢了舞鞋*
*The moon threatened to dance her out of her shoes*
*他耳边就要响起*
*In his ear was about to hear*
*难以抗拒的可怕想法*
*An awful thought he could not refuse*
*她说  难道  难道*
*She said Don't Don't...*
*你不想吗  你不想吗*
*Don't you wanna? Don't you wanna*
*今晚就坠入爱河*
*Wanna fall in love tonight*
*你难道  难道不想*
*Don't Don't...Don't you wanna? Don't you wanna*
*今晚就坠入爱河*
*Wanna fall in love tonight*
*她说*
*She said*
*躲在塔夫绸下*
*Underneath the taffeta*
*不是没有更好的藏身之处*
*There ain't no better hiding place*
*如若看见月光  我会开怀大笑*
*If I see the moon, I'll just laugh it up*
*想要一醒来  就看见你美丽的脸*
*Want to wake up to your, your pretty face*
*难道  难道你不想*
*Don't? Don't? Don't you wanna? Don't you wanna*
*今晚就坠入爱河*
*Wanna fall in love tonight?*
刚刚...
Did that...
是不是真的
happen?
-是的  -是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
没错
Oh, yeah.
所以我们刚刚和王子跳舞了
So we just danced with Prince?
-和王子一起  -是的
- With Prince. - Yeah.
-没错  -真的很有趣
- That's right. - That was fun.
杰茜  你是怎么知道歌词的
Jess, how did you know the words?
我觉得王子是有魔力的
I think Prince is magic.
我一直都觉得王子有魔力
I've always thought Prince was magic.
接下来怎么办
Where do we go from here?
我们要怎么继续生活
How do we move on from this?
明天还是去工作吗
Just go to work tomorrow?
等一下
Wait a minute.
希希呢
Where's Cece?
-我会对你手下留情的  -谢谢
- I'll take it easy on you. - Thank you.
你想赌点钱吗
You want to put some money on this?